(Howard:)I think you're gonna be really happy
with this security camera.
(Howard:)The optics are great.
It's got infrared technology.
(Howard:)And there's even a backup battery
when the power goes out.
(Raj:)Whatever. I can see my little princess
while I'm at work, right?
Why can't you watch porn
like a regular guy?
Give me your laptop so I can
configure the software.
(Raj:)Hold on. This is weird.
(Howard:)What?
(Raj:)I was Googling that girl I've been dating
and found her blog.
(Howard:)Cool. Anything juicy?
(Raj:)She said she recently went
on a date with a guy named Roger.
(Raj:)And he's Indian.
And he's an astrophysicist too!
- You know what's going on, don't you?
- Yes.
Mommy was right.
American girls are sexually voracious devils.
(Howard:)I can't believe I have to explain this.
People change names on blogs...
...to protect their privacy. "Roger" is Raj.